title,entities
"Fox News: McConnell believes Trump committed impeachable offenses, supports Democrats' impeachment efforts:","[('Fox News', 'ORG'), ('McConnell', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Democrats', 'NORP')]"
House impeaches Trump for second time over Capitol riots,"[('House', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Capitol', 'ORG')]"
Republican Starting To Think Trump Might Not Pull Off A Last-Minute 4D Chess Move,"[('Republican', 'NORP')]"
Romney rips Trump over Capitol Hill mayhem: 'This is what the president has caused',"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Capitol Hill', 'ORG')]"
"Elon accuses Trump of being in Epstein files, Trump says Elon was asked to leave","[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'LOC'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Elon', 'PERSON')]"
"Genuinely, please help me understand",[]
Trump Administration To Start Transition Process For Biden,"[('Trump Administration To Start Transition Process For Biden', 'ORG')]"
Trump calls for delay to 2020 US election,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
"After Being Kicked Off Social Media, Trump Forced To Go Door To Door And Shout 'RIGGED ELECTION!'","[('Being Kicked Off Social', 'PERSON'), ('Trump Forced To Go Door', 'ORG')]"
Capitol rioters could face up to 10 years in prison under Trump monument executive order,"[('Capitol', 'ORG'), ('up to 10 years', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
"Why the Biden Administration Fired Staffers Over Smoking Pot But Let Kamala Harris Get Away With It -- Under drug criminalization, elites often get away with the same behavior that earns disadvantaged people harsh punishments.","[('the Biden Administration Fired Staffers Over Smoking Pot', 'ORG'), ('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON')]"
BREAKING: Kamala Harris Selects Gov. Tim Walz As Running Mate,"[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('Tim Walz', 'PERSON')]"
Kamala Harris is a terrible VP pick but this is still so true. God bless this country!,"[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON')]"
Kamala Harris' 'I'm not here to say I told you so' jibe in her first major statement against Trump administration,"[(""Kamala Harris' '"", 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
Kamala Harris Destroyed,"[('Kamala Harris Destroyed', 'PERSON')]"
Kamala Harris claims she had ‘key role’ in removing US troops from Afghanistan – but now silent since Taliban took power,"[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('Taliban', 'ORG')]"
Washington Post erased Kamala Harris' crass joke about inmates from a 2019 story — then put it back after they got caught,"[('Washington Post', 'ORG'), (""Kamala Harris'"", 'PERSON'), ('2019', 'DATE')]"
"Kamala Harris’ father: ""She's playing identity politics. We wish to categorically dissociate ourselves from this travesty.""","[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON')]"
Collage created with the photos of black males Kamala Harris prosecuted and put in prison,"[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON')]"
Joining some liberals today.,"[('today', 'DATE')]"
